[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
AN OLD DRAGON'S WRATH
[mysterious music playing]
- [female panther] Hey, young man.
- [Legoshi] Hmm?
How would you like to try a special
energy drink, just for carnivores?
Uh, I'm okay. I have more stamina
than you would think.
Nah, come on, just trust me.
You'll love it. You can try one.
It won't hurt. Here.
[fizzes]
Oh. No, no. I should probably go...
I... [sniffs]
Huh?
[sniffs, moans]
[male panther chuckles]
We'll have this kid hooked in no time.
[groaning]
[inhaling]
- [sneezes]
- [both exclaim in disgust]
- [coughs] Sorry, it was cold last night.
- [female panther] Are you kidding?
And I slept in only my underwear, so, uh...
Yeah.
Yeah, anyway, that energy drink of yours,
it contains herbivore blood
and bone tissue, I believe.
[male black panther] Uh...
Sorry, not interested.
Well, see ya.
- Whoa, wait.
- [lizard] What's up with him?
[Legoshi] Just let it go.
It's for the best
that you don't get involved.
[inhales heavily] This kind of thing
happens all the time in the real world.
[Louis] Is that really
how you feel, Legoshi?
[Legoshi] Hmm?
[Louis] You went so far as to eat my leg
for the sake of justice,
yet you're going to let them get away
with trying to hustle someone like that?
[gasps softly]
It's time to get angry, Legoshi.
[Legoshi] If you think it'll help, Louis.
Uh... What's your deal, man?
[Legoshi] Well,
I ate my friend while he was still alive.
I only react to the flesh
of living herbivores,
but I want, more than anything,
to get along with those living herbivores.
You keep wagging that tongue
and I'll cut it out!
Have you ever, even once,
thought about the lives of the herbivores
that end up in that drink you're selling?
Or do they mean nothing to you?
Huh?
What are you, a softie? You really need
to embrace your nature, kid.
- [growls]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
[exhales]
[Legoshi] "Embrace your nature"?
"Embrace your nature."
[heart beating, laughing]
[male panther] What are you
laughing about, you freak?
[grunts]
[groans]
- [gasps]
- Huh.
[Legoshi] Oh, I'll embrace my nature
for the sake of the herbivores.
- [growls]
- [gasps]
[yelling]
[both grunting]
[panther yells, grunts]
[groaning]
[both grunting]
[groans]
- [Legoshi grunting]
- [groaning]
[both grunting]
[Legoshi] My fangs are bared.
My heart is going to beat out of my chest.
- [growling]
- I quit, I give up. We won't sell it!
- [groans, whimpers]
- [Legoshi] I can't hear you.
[choking]
[Legoshi] For the sake of the herbivores,
I have to destroy him.
- [grunts]
- [female panther gasps]
[female panther] Stop already!
[Legoshi] My whole body is screaming,
"Go ahead, embrace your true nature!"
- [whimpering]
- [Legoshi] Hmm.
- [grunting]
- [male panther groaning]
[siren approaching]
Huh?
[female panther] Let's get out of here!
[officer] Hey, stop right there! Hey!
You there! Hey, wait!
SHISHI-GUMI
[Free] Hey, why do you think
they stuck you and me out here
to collect the revenue, huh?
Not like I care. Think about it like this.
We get to get out from under
that creepy new boss for a while.
- [lizard panting]
- Hey! Right here.
[lizard panting]
You assholes, how long did you plan
to keep us waiting?
That's everything.
That's all you got in one day?
Who cares, man?
This isn't what they said it was.
What what was?
Kines, the energy drink.
You said just a whiff
and they'd all come running, right?
We had this wolf kid, he just walked away.
[both] Huh.
- What kind of carnivore...
- Yeah, that's a little strange.
Want to hear "strange"?
He came back and started ranting about
payback for the sacrificed herbivores
and went on a total rampage.
[lizard] Damn him. He'll pay for that.
What do you think?
Should we go back and let the boss know?
[Free] Hmm.
[gasps] Hey!
- [lizard] Sorry, tell them I tried!
- [both] Huh?
[serene music playing]
[Bill] Okay, listen up.
In light of the separate education
for herbivores and carnivores,
mixed club activities like ours
have been banned.
Anyway, we're here today
so that we can discuss and decide
on the future of the drama club together.
- Anybody got a question?
- [Kai] Yeah.
Why are you acting like
you're the real president around here?
- What's the deal, dude?
- Doesn't suit you.
[Bill groans] Shut up, would ya?
He's right. Be respectful.
HAVE SEPARATE CLUBS
OR SUSPEND THE CLUB
Bill is our legitimate president.
Louis chose him to run the club.
[Kai] Uh, okay, then in that case,
I vote to cease club activities for now.
Huh?
Louis, who stood up to a devourer alone,
appointed you, a carnivore.
He could've chosen anyone. But it was you.
In that case,
why cave and divide the club into two
when, instead, we could protest
the whole school?
When'd you get so smart?
But if we do that, we may never
be able to do club activities again.
[sighs] Good point.
What are you saying? We've always
done well in here as a mixed group.
We can use that
to persuade the school. Duh.
Always done well?
- Do you think that's true?
- Huh?
I'm sorry to say it, but there were two
major incidents in here last year alone.
I'm not convinced that
that counts as us "doing well."
- That's a little out of line.
- No, it's not. It's the truth.
Our club is the whole reason
they're splitting us up.
They can't risk us getting hurt again.
[Fudge] Oh, I get it. You're saying
carnivores are to blame for everything.
[Ellen] What? That's not what I said.
Okay, let's just chill out.
[both sigh]
What do you think, Juno?
Coexistence.
All of us working together.
I think the most important thing
is that we do not allow the principles
of existing together to die out now.
[sighs]
If you take a look around, you'll see that
our club was founded on those principles.
For us to create art and harmony.
That was the spirit.
And if we share in that spirit,
we're still one club, even if we're apart.
And you may not agree,
but I think it's important to try.
Keep the fire, even if that means
we do have to separate for a little while.
She's got a point.
That's Juno for you.
[Pina] If that's the tactic
we're going with, then I'm out.
- [all] Huh?
- What, did I stutter?
It's been a good six months,
but it's time to move on.
See, I'm not into the whole
long-distance thing.
"Absence makes the heart grow fonder."
I mean, has that ever worked out?
And you know what?
This club and meeting you carnivores
has taught me something about myself.
All that power you have is so enticing.
Those sharp claws and fangs of yours
make me all tingly.
[shudders] I can't get enough of it.
Alas, if we're going to split up,
there's no point in me staying.
So I'm out.
[all sigh, exclaim]
Bye. Take care. See you around.
[door opens]
- You don't need to say it.
- [door closes]
What?
"If only Louis were still here with us."
You were thinking it.
[sighs] You're right.
[metal creaking]
[grunts softly]
What the...
[gasps softly] Legoshi.
[gasps] Oh, hey, Haru!
[Haru chuckles]
- What's going on?
- [Legoshi chuckles]
[both chuckle]
Huh? What is it?
- [chuckles] You look so cute.
- [giggles]
Come on, is that the best you can do?
[both chuckle]
Are you off of work today?
We didn't talk about hanging out.
- Mmm, yeah, that's true.
- Huh?
- [sighs softly]
- It's okay, I won't ask.
And I can see
you're already healing up anyway, so...
Uh, oh, this? It's nothing.
[chuckles nervously] I just hit my face.
- Uh... Hmm?
- Never mind that.
Listen, I came here 'cause there's
something I've been meaning to tell you.
Because I want to be honest
with you, Haru.
Hmm?
The thing is...
Mmm-hmm?
Well, I, uh... I...
[bus stops]
There's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
- You said that.
- Oh, yeah.
- Well...
- [Haru's father] Haru!
- [Haru gasps]
- Huh?
- Watch yourself, wolf!
- [gasps nervously]
Thank you so much
for picking up my change, sir!
- You're a lifesaver! Bye!
- Uh... Huh?
- [pants]
- Wait.
[Haru] You're early today. Hi, Dad.
[gasps] That's her dad?
Yeah. Have you still not gotten
a bus pass?
Uh, there was kind of a mix-up,
so my student ID is coming
a bit later than I thought.
- [Haru's father] That's unfortunate...
- I didn't even get to say hello.
I guess being a carnivore means
some things are just going to be
more... difficult.
- [Haru] And you know you don't need to.
- [Haru's father] Is that so?
MAI MAI MILK
[choking, whimpering]
Listen up, and remember this.
The reason our society functions at all
is because we herbivores
have been extremely tolerant.
[grunts, groans]
I'm here for when the goodwill runs out.
[spluttering] I'm so sorry. Please.
I'll send them home by 8. [whimpers]
You've been warned.
- [snow leopard whimpers] Understood.
- [cows speaking indistinctly]
You've been suffering under him
for too long.
I should've been here much sooner.
Please forgive me.
- [cow 1] Thank you, thank you again.
- [cow 2] So glad you came.
[Corne] Mr. Yahya.
[Yahya] What did you find out?
[Corne] Well, the gray wolf
who got into that big brawl
with the Kines dealers in the alley?
He is for sure the same young beast
you read about.
You know, the one who ate
his friend's leg in January?
Yes, I kind of had a feeling.
There's something about this guy.
Yeah, like, does he think
he's a vigilante or something?
Not like we need one. Beastar like you
has got the city covered, Mr. Yahya.
That may be, but there's a limit
to what one old horse can do
when it comes down to protecting the city.
[Corne] Now, hold on.
Don't get me wrong, I'm glad for the help.
Because if I can't rid the streets
of that energy drink,
the public safety I've been working
all these years for is still way off.
[Yahya] A horse's field of vision is ever
so slightly short of absolute panoramic.
350 degrees to be exact.
If I could make up for
that ten-degree blind spot,
the dregs of society
would have nowhere left to hide.
The criminals that operate in the shadows
are taunting me.
If I had the 360-degree field of vision
like I used to when you were here,
I'd be able to annihilate them
once and for all.
My gentle monster...
[inhales heavily] you ruined it all.
The idea of a perfect fighting force,
the perfect society,
building perfect trust, gone forever.
It may be only ten degrees,
but it's still ten degrees from perfect,
Gosha.
[sighs]
I feel like every time I take
a step closer to Haru,
I wind up taking another step back.
[sighs] It's not fair that
maintaining a bond with another species
has to be so complicated.
Hmm?
[mysterious music playing]
A lizard. Revenge for yesterday?
[sizzling]
[Legoshi] Hmm?
Hmm.
[gasps softly]
[gasps, gulps]
[Legoshi groans softly]
[gulps]
A Komodo dragon's venom
doesn't affect its own kind.
Hmm.
- Legoshi! How the hell are ya?
- [Legoshi chuckles]
Hi, Grandpa. How about
a normal greeting next time?
Surely, you don't mind
a bit of your old granddad's venom?
You're my only grandchild.
Who else am I supposed to mess with?
I know.
[quirky music playing]
[Legoshi] That venom that can bring death
to many other creatures,
but, to me, it's always tasted like
a bittersweet marmalade.
[Gosha] Hey, you still like french fries,
don't ya?
Huh? Oh, uh, yeah, sure.
- All right then, let's go eat some.
- Uh... now?
Yeah, now!
[Legoshi] I liked them a lot more
when I was a child
I mean, it's not like
they're anything special now.
[Gosha laughs] So this is chilly for you?
[Legoshi] Kind of.
It's fine.
We don't have to talk about anything.
[music ends]
- Why don't we just sit by the door?
- Hmm?
Not busy in here.
We don't have to head
straight for the back. Come on.
[hesitates] No, but I...
Legoshi, don't tell me
you've already forgotten the rule.
In a restaurant, we always choose a table
somewhere in the back.
Don't want to cause trouble.
A venomous Komodo dragon like me
tends to bring out the worst in people.
Best not to tempt fate.
It's just how it is.
[Legoshi] I've always found it
kind of weird.
You shouldn't have to sit in the back.
I mean, it's not like
you've done anything wrong.
[groans softly]
- [owner] It's fine, sit down.
- [both] Huh?
[Gosha grunts softly]
[cutlery clattering]
- [Gosha] Dig in, it's your favorite.
- [Legoshi] Um...
I'm... I'm sorry
I dropped out of school. Is...
Is that why you're here?
[sighs] What's going on with you?
You've got all these huge scars
across your face.
- You ought to be coming to me for advice.
- I don't want to do that.
My mom needed your help before,
and you didn't give it to her, did you?
Now, hold on...
I need you to know that
I am grateful that you raised me,
but from now on,
I want to take care of myself.
[Gosha] Mmm.
[eagle 1] You know what you want?
[eagle 2] Whatever I got last time
was good. What was that?
How should I know? I'm not your mom.
I understand.
You're a grown man after all.
But promise me
you'll remember what I taught you.
Rather, what I would've liked
to teach you.
What I always tried to teach you.
[Legoshi] Be a pacifist. Right?
- I would never forget.
- Hmm.
Good lad.
[both] Hmm?
[eagle 1] Yo.
Who let a venomous slug like you
sit in the good seats?
Diner's filling up, old man.
How about we find you a more suitable seat
before you stink up the place?
- Yeah.
- Sorry?
- What? Hmm?
- Huh?
[chair clatters]
Legoshi, let's go. Legoshi!
I didn't really understand
what you meant there.
Are you suggesting
Komodo venom is somehow airborne?
- Because that's not true.
- Huh?
You know what he meant, you mutt.
What, do you want to go?
Yeah, I'm happy to take it outside.
Legoshi...
[both snarling]
[owner] I'm only going to say this once.
We expect all of our customers
to follow the rules.
Those who do not
will be kindly asked to leave.
[grunts]
Consider yourself lucky
the owner's a reptile.
- [eagle 1] Let's get out of this place.
- [eagle 2] I didn't wanna eat here anyway.
[owner] Unbelievable.
Excuse me, uh, do you do ant shakes here?
- Best in town.
- Oh, great.
- I'd like a medium, please.
- [Gosha] Legoshi...
- When are you going to learn?
- [owner] Coming right up.
[Gosha] Tell me something.
What part of the word "pacifism"
do you not understand?
That was different. I can't back down
on a situation like that. It's wrong.
I'm not going to sit back and watch
like when I was a child.
Oh, right, because you're so grown up now.
[Legoshi sighs]
Look, if you want to survive
in this society,
then get this through your thick skull.
In situations like that,
just let it slide.
You're not going to solve any problems
with fighting!
- [flapping]
- Huh?
Huh? Huh.
[eagles grunt]
- [eagle 1 sneers]
- Huh? [grunts]
Yo. You made me look like an ass
back there, you know that?
[groans softly]
Kind of sucks for you that you've wandered
into this secluded alleyway.
Do you know what time it is?
- Time for a lesson in etiquette!
- [Legoshi grunts]
- [gasps]
- [Gosha grunts]
- [Gosha growls]
- [eagle 1 gasps]
Keep your mitts off my grandson!
[yells in pain]
[snarls] Those feathers of yours
are so soft and pretty.
You're lucky I haven't sprayed them
with my poison.
Damn you!
[both grunt]
Mmm, you know what they say.
When you've got it, you've got it.
[gasps]
Grandpa...
Who are you?
[special closing theme song playing]